In the window of the library, double-click to open the practice files folder and find cdetails.
Open the adding refs folder.
In the address refs folder, double-click to drag it into the 2D or 3D window.
In the 2D tool bar, select the
In the window of the 2D window, double-click to open the practice files folder and drag it into the 3D or 3D window.
In the tool bar, select the
In the panel, select , and open the panel.
Use the tool to divide the edge and the bottom of the panel.
In the window, use the tool to select the edge panel.
Press and copy the edge.
In the blank, press and paste the edge.
Use the tool to divide the edge and the bottom of the panel.
In the window, use the tool to select the edge panel.
Press and copy the edge.
In the blank, press and copy the edge.
Use the tool to divide the edge.
In the window, use the tool to select the edge.
Press and copy the edge.
Use the tool to divide the edge.
In the 2D Toolbar, select the Rectangular Tool.
In the 2D window, press the left-hand button in the blank area.
Click on the number frame, enter the value, and click OK.
In the 2D toolbar, select the Rectangular Toolbar.
In the Rectangular Toolbar, select the highlighted article.
Click on the number frame, enter the value, and click OK.
Repeat the operation on the Comicges participant.
Use the Wongji Superman toolcap Poly由 AnyTable with磨刺嫩
For nevertheless世界完整的文型 speculation in the toolbar,
Click on the button to create a starting point.
The mouse will move.
Click on the button again to complete the baseline.
Click on the half of the screen that needs to be rotated.
The mouse will stop at the half of the screen.
It will show in light blue.
Click on the mouse to select.
Right-click to visit the extension window.
You can enter the distance or angle.
Then click OK.
Repeat the operation in other parts.
Use the tool to select the line and point on the outline line.
Click on the point.
Select the menu about points.
Change to the curve point.
Use the tool to delete the excess red curve points on the outline.
Use the tool to separate the edge of the curve and the edge of the sleeve.
Click on the edge of the 3D window.
Select Add to Side in the menu.
Use the tool to separate the edge of the curve and the edge of the sleeve.
Use the tool to select the outline line of the sleeve.
Use the tool to select the outline line of the blueprints.
Press and hold theos letter .
To see A3D clear.
Put it on the other side
Use the positioning ball tool in the 3D window
Put the symmetrical plate on the model wrist
Use the line sewing tool to sew the edge and the sleeve
Activated simulation will be used in 3D clothing